Come to the night, the car is laid out for show
Star shine is so bright, watch the secret sun fall
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the future holds
we are king
I've been missing in my sleep
He's eating
Yo, welcome to the madness, buckle in tight
the day that's like the way kids don't look away your shadows talk and it came
to stay we laugh we cry we speak we scream live from the madness this ain't
no dream
So here's a little song to make it real clear
No hate speech, don't test that line
Don't care if it's soft or your hard, our time
You say it, you gone, don't play confused
This ain't that show, we don't make those moves
No slander, yeah, I said what I said
You toss more fake dirt than a Reddit thread
WWE got nothing on this chat
False accusations, man, cut that crap
The hate
avatar somebody's face real names real pics this ain't your place posting
addresses like it's halloween you better send pizza with that scheme no
nudity we beg and plead Aldi no one wants your balls on screen flirty diamond
stop the solo acts those melted kisses ain't bringing sexy back
This ain't your bathroom concert tour. This ain't your only fans preview. This is Psyche Awakens.
A sacred space where trolls come to die and souls come to shine. I don't come to your house
and poop on the table, so don't come to mine and drop a deuce on my panel. Respect the host,
respect the guests, or get digitally dragged, publicly blessed. Amen.
Whoa
Hold on guys
Oh shit, hold on
Hello
I'm here. I mean gosh guys this one play a song. I was trying to get it ready for you guys
It's everyone left and god. It's just sharks
It's okay though.
I need to fix the song.
Obviously, it refers to me as a female.
I did not catch that on the
lyrics.
I'm going to redo it.
I like the lyrics. I'll be right back.
Oh, goodness gracious.
I'm not gonna leave you guys bored here. I'll play it again. I'll play this page on your we're back. I'm right back promise
I've been missing in my sleep
He's eating steak, somewhere in the middle they both take a break
He'd trade his knife stick for a fishing pole
Chase her laughter like it's his patrol page
Don't you know you're the catch of the day
And this cop's got one hell of a line to say
Okay, I did it guys, hold on, I'm gonna take a while.
Hi, what's up?
Propaganda, not Propaganda, I'll be right back.
I'm trying to do this real quick.
If I have something else to play, I don't, really, here.
Watch this for a second.
Alex, what are you gonna do to me if you pull me over
and I've been speeding on the freeway?
What are you gonna do to me?
I'm gonna say sir, license registration. I'm gonna pretend it's bad. I'm gonna say step out of the car
And I'm gonna throw you in the bushes in the bushes. I'm gonna fuck the shit out of you in the bushes
Okay, oh my god. I'm gonna in the in the trees on the side of the highway
I'm gonna fucking just give it to you and then that's it my man
I'm gonna make hot car and just fall my way
in the trees, but on the side of the highway,
I'm gonna fucking just give it to you.
And then that's it, my man.
I'm gonna get in my top car and just go on my way.
Unless you wanna go to jail,
I can just handcuff you to get to jail,
or I can fuck you on the side of the highway.
It's up to you, my man.
Okay, hey guys, Alice we call her controversial,
but Alice, he's a sweet guy, he's a sweet guy.
I'm very sweet, my sweetheart.
My lollipop you gonna make me like a lollipop. How many legs does it take to get to the middle of a tootsie pop?
Alex can I try can I can I lick your tootsie pop Alex? Oh, yeah, baby. Oh my god. Okay. I got it. I love this guy
This good. This good. He's my he's my he's my cutie, but he's my he's my cutie, buddy
He gets in that you in a place, you know for me handcuffs in the bed and he f's the f out of me
Oh shit. Oh my gosh. That was embarrassing. Oh my gosh. I remember that day
It was an interesting day
Because I I would write that I swear I'm so almost ready. It's almost ready
I promise you I'll be back. Okay. I'll be right there. I'm gonna send it early. No, I'm ready. No, I'm ready now
I have it ready here. I got it. I'm gonna add it real quick. Oh
My god, this better not take a long time one. Okay
I got it I got it guys don't leave me don't leave me don't leave me. I'm trying to like do as best as I can
Yeah, I found it. Oh
Okay, it's working it's working you guys ready to hear the new song so this is a new song, okay?
It's almost done. It's processing. It's almost done. Just watch a second. You'll love it. You'll love it. It's such one
Yeah, these trolls there. There you go
Here you go guys, this is from your new psyche waking song enjoy
No hate speech don't test that line don't care if it's soft day to hard our time you say it you gone
Don't play confused this ain't that show we don't make those moves no slander
Yeah, I said what I said you toss more fake dirt than a reddit thread
WWE got nothing on this chat false accusations man cut that crap be hey
to the vibe and don't do dumb things why's your avatar somebody's face real names real pics
this ain't your place posting addresses like it's halloween you better send pizza with that scheme
no nudity we beg and plead i'll dee no one wants your balls on screen flirty diamonds stop the
solo act those melted kisses ain't bringing sexy back
Don't behave yourself, it ain't that hard
Nah, don't be the chaos in my ta-
and time begins.
Good what's up guys hold on hi guys you like that
Okay, I did my best I did my best on that it will be spanking time. Oh, I'll get I got this later
I get there we go. What's up guys here? I am here. I am the one that you love the one that you did
Remember that song and that's a good song. Let me plug this light in
Yeah, I mean it's a cute. I think that was cute. I mean I think I fixed it a little bit
It did bleep out the word dicks. I don't know why I did it on the first time, but second time
I guess it was too much for it, but it still is a good song
Guys if you think I'm not good at good AI, you know, just listen to that song
Oh, what's that? Oh
Guys also I was showing some stuff today. I don't know if you've seen this. I
Mean I'm doing the tarot card deck the psyche awakens tarot deck
So first I was doing the lovers and I was like, you know trying to do spunky
Just and think they're in the devil car, but I made this lovers
It's similar to the devil car
So it came up with this first which is like kind of disappointing. I was like, okay
I think it's a little bit simple. I think I wanted it better illustrated like more detail
Because it is like, you know, it is good. I mean it's good. It got basically me as the angel and Raphael and there's you know, they're in the
Adam and Eve kind of thing, they're all covered up.
Okay, so I said, do a better detail.
So they did this one.
Whoa, that's what I'm talking about.
That's what I was looking for, right?
The more realistic, oh, look at it.
He looks pretty good there too.
So that was better.
I think there's me too.
And there's this, look, it says S plus J,
I think it's funky plus Justin.
Okay, so that was cute.
Okay, do you want to see the other cute one I did?
I was like, okay, so it's like doing the Wheel of Fortune card.
I was like, do the Wheel of Fortune, but you know.
I don't know if you won't know who this is, but I was like, oh, let me and Emma playing like Wheel of Fortune the game
Emma Leviathan, right? So first they did
this
And it's like okay
I was like well as like we're not as like me as we look like we're sitting in quarters
It's like make us look like we're like having fun on like a game show like we're excited, right? So they made this one
Okay, so it's a little bit better, but I was like still I was like there's something missing from it as like as the can you just
Do it like you know a little bit bigger like we know we're spinning the wheel it's a game
We're playing the game show. Okay, and so here's the final one they do with that one
Pretty good, I mean I'm impressed wheel of fortune. Okay
Finally I was like, okay, let's do one more car. Let's try the start during rough draft of the tower and
Tower car that I have it here. Where is it?
Oh, yeah, okay, and I think and put me in Vita. They said a bit. There's a couple people fall off in the building
I said, tell me in Vita doing it. Let's make those stars of the card. So here's the tower with Vita and I
So
Hope you like that. I mean, it's like pretty cool. I think they're pretty cool
I think that I like that that actually the tower card and maybe called the towers
Maybe called the towers, but call the tower card and there's the eye. I mean, it's like it's just perfect, right?
Do you like it?
If you work you come early, I don't know but I think they used these the I don't care if sick one so like it said once the link
You know sick can talk to me nicely. I don't know the sick has to listen to that
He has to like take a test on the on the psyche spanking song
Honest questions. He basically has told you go in every way possible. Will you ever let her so like her so much?
I'm not just being so
So Sweepie you're saying so I haven't bothered her. I haven't gone to her. I haven't talked to her once
Talk I haven't written a contact anyway
Am I that is still like somebody she is a celebrity she is a
The tower is very sick. You like it. Okay. Yeah, she's a celebrity
She has 25,000 YouTube subscribers. So she's a public figure
So I'm allowed to like her still and I can post I can use her image in my tarot card
Yeah, maybe it's not her. Maybe it's someone that looks just like her. Maybe it's not her. Okay. You're the one
It tells us all the yeah, I know I tell you the truth about it, but I'm not like supposed to be like
Bothering her. Okay. I'm making a card and that's beta in this card. It's not even Emma
It was in the Wheel of Fortune being like a little like a not to the sucky this thing. Yeah, it doesn't look like her
Okay, so chill chill. It doesn't look like her
Looks like her be it has me blocked. Yeah, but I scum are you treating to block yourself?
Okay, the sweet feet, but I'm just saying you're like being very personal about it
Like I'm allowed to like anybody. I was not I'm not bothering or anybody
I don't know. It's like you're making it sound like I'm doing something bad, but I'm not
We're allowed to like anybody you think it's funny. Okay, I
Don't know if you yeah, so shit you but then log in to your
You need to chill. Oh, yeah, you do you need to chill sweet feet you do because you know what you're a little bit of a
You're a little bit mean sometimes you're a little bit like oh, I'm just gonna make fun of psyche like oh, you know
Yeah, I'm just gonna make fun of him, but then it's like oh, it's a joke. You know, that's what people that's what psychopaths say
Oh, it's just a joke. I'm just joking about right when I say, you know, you're gonna choke on it to death on a honey drizzle biscuit
Okay
Okay, well, I already made it but I didn't mean to bother you or you think you think I'm over right. Okay, sweet PMS
Hey, I'm a sweet baby. It's just humor. It's just you don't worry. I'm not overreacting
That's how much that's how much I'm overreacting is to get chill
Okay. Oh, you never said you were joking. Oh, so you're serious. Oh, so you're a serious. Okay, sweetie
I see how you are now. Can I give a sports recap? Yeah, it's like oh the 49ers are lost
Football's over guys. Let's forget all about it. Football is done
Anyway suppose we got
How about that is that good I'm sorry I'm sorry guys
But how are you? Did you like this song though? I'm gonna play it like a little bit late when more people come in when there's 20 people coming in
They did it was true. Yeah, I'm pretty good. I am pretty good at sports
It's okay, I'm not mad at anybody. I'm not bad. It's didn't dude. You're making
You're not making sense. I will not ever ask you that question again. Thank you. Please don't I get very sensitive around
Questions about Emma because I'm upset
Okay
He did me wrong. Okay
Who would have thought a succubus would do an ignorant man wrong? Okay, I don't go live as much as I used to
Oh, I think like the audience has kind of turned on me a little bit. It's not as much
You know if it was like cool, like you know, but no it's like every even if I get a donation
Oh my god, it's like I can't you know what I have one person that's donating to me and I get you know
And people are like mad about that. I mean
Yeah, I don't know it's okay. It's okay. It's okay. We're just joking
Let's see Tom flat and it is show he wants to come up
Well, Tom flash is banned from the show because he put like CP out on the poor mom like a couple times
And he kept trying to do it, so he's not coming up
He didn't hear the psyche song obviously
It's it's not allowed
that is really disgusting and
I'm flat. I mean he was like okay Tom flash is like this character
It's like he's like he's not really he doesn't it's like a joke. It's a joke character. I don't impose links
No, I don't why do I want the troll said is by me so easily if I the psyche song. Oh, okay, you never last
Losses we've always been here. Well, I don't know love you. Don't talk
I'll play the song again, but I went away for 20 people to come in the chat before I play it again
It is a psych. It's a new psyche. There's a rule song
I'm not I'm not even moderate. I'll make you a moderator sweepy. You're the first member. I
Don't forget that sweepy. I love you, but it's like you're so mean to me
It's like you're not I was like your name is sweepy, but you're not so sweet sometimes you're like, you know
You're like that baby on Popeye. He's named a sweepie and you think oh, it's gonna be nice
It's a minute. It's a miniature Popeye. All it is is Popeye like as a baby and he's mean
Okay, okay, they got it who that's okay. Well, I mean it was sick cuz sick is always sick wants to go on panel sick I
Promoted your stupid rumble show enough. Okay. I know you get 20 viewers a show. Okay. Okay, so I get like
500 or more. Okay, like a thousand. So
You're milking my show for all you can't say. Okay. I know. Okay. It's fine
Say, how about you throw a sponsor panel one time, you know, 10 bucks out of a year
You can before that, you know, $10 bottle of vodka
Oh, sweetie, don't take it so seriously. You get so you get so you're so sensitive. I mean, it's like this is called
Come it's called improvisational comedy. Maybe you won't think it's funny, but I think it's fucking funny. Okay
Well people in chat, okay
So anyway, you have a left the audience has left
Well, nobody's coming here anymore and then it's like people that do I think today
I was like begging people on the panel. It's like the panel is open. I was like a ghost paid for it open
I don't know if there was nobody wants to talk to him or no one was talk to me
No, let's talk to me anymore
Hey, everyone's mad at me for like nothing. It's like what oh my god, someone donated money to you
Well, I'm sorry. I'm gonna make it the show better because of it
The sweepy look at how you react you're acting you're overreacting like remember it should be like oh, okay
He's a joke or it's a joke or you get seriously
It's not gonna be like I'm gonna sit here argue about whether it's a joke or not or like, you know
How offended am I gonna be about it?
Whatever whatever
I can't worry about everybody's little feelings anymore. Oh my gosh, my feelings were hurt feelings aren't a thing
They're like an idea. So some idea in your head had a little
Narcissistic injury. Oh, I won. I apologize. Okay, so sorry. Yeah, I get injuries, too
You know, yeah, it's not easy being here 10 hours and then you know, you pull by to delete the episode everything's everything's gone. Oh
I'm pretty but look but guys. She's not reacting. Who's the only one comment?
You see even when care sweepy if you don't care if you don't care
You know if they say if you if you if you react that's saying to this you keep repeat you keep replying to my thing
You're supposed to say okay. I get it
He's trolling me. That's what to say. Oh, but I did this I did that I do that governor
I'm sorry. That was a bad English accent. I'm sorry. I did not mean to
Okay, I'm the trouble now
The only one talking to you because everyone's scared of you right now you're yelling I'm not yelling guys my scary person my scary
I'm just like this gay. I'm gonna say the nicest gay person you ever meet like really. I'm a gay person doesn't care if you like
Call me f a ggoc. I don't care. I mean it's like I'm like the chillest gay person in the world and it's like
Don't know hi. I'm not scared. Hey, Electra, but here I want to play now electors here. So
She counts as like 10 people to me because I love her so much. So here's the song again. I'll play the song one more time
Here's a rule. It's a rules by chat in a song who'd be entertained. I love you guys
Trolls and tarot where the vibes are wild and the rules
They're simple, but y'all can't seem to follow
So here's a little song to make it real clear
No hate speech, don't test that line
Don't care if it's soft data, hard art time
You say it, you gone, don't play confused
This ain't that show, we don't make those moves
No slander, yeah I said what I said
You toss more fake dirt than a Reddit thread
WWE got nothing on this chat, false accusations
Man, cut that crap
Behave
To the vibe and don't do dumb things
Why's your avatar somebody's face real names real pics this ain't your place posting addresses like it's Halloween
You better send pizza with that scheme. No nudity. We beg and plead Aldi
No one wants your balls on screen flirty diamond stop the solo act those melted kisses ain't bringing sexy back
to the vibe and don't do dumb things this ain't your bathroom concert tour this ain't your only
fans preview this is psyche awakens a sacred space where trolls come to die and souls come to shine
i don't come to your house and poop on the table so don't come to mine and drop a deuce on my
panel respect the host respect the guests or get digitally dragged publicly blessed amen
Don't behave yourself, it ain't that hard
Nah, don't be the chaos in my tarot
bank and time begins
That's so good. How catchy do you like that one?
It's baking time. Yes. I'm getting a paddle. I have I have it. I'm just making out of wood
Hey guys band sweepy. I see almost almost almost. She's pushing it. Hi guys
I love sweepy. Actually, she's like get a sweepy is the first member. I'm not gonna be mad at sweepy
She's my first the first member of the show
It's like a love love thing. It was like I love sweepy. So it's the whole thing
You think I'm gonna forget my first member am I Emma Levi again? I'm gonna forget my first member
Who's a member for six months?
Well, I won't do a sweepy don't threaten me with a good time a
Mod will do it if you annoy them enough. So they'll stop annoying the mods Joe's name in a mod. Okay
Watch out for that a lecture woman. I'm just kidding. She's fine
Bad me, bad me dead, bad me.
I'm doing the British accent.
Bad me, psyche, bad me dead, bad me dead.
Is that what you sound like right now?
I'm just saying.
No, I'm just kidding.
I love you all, I love all you guys.
I love all you guys.
Hey, but did you like the song?
That was a, I think it was not a bad attempt.
I mean, the first time I did it,
I put, I kind of liked the music in the first one.
It was a female singer, but I admit it was psyche was a she
Also didn't really work
So now I've gone right, but they believe the word six
You're not pretty ish. I'm not pretty. I love you. Are you sure? Yeah, you're gonna access it. I'm so sorry. I
Thought you're a British, okay
You like the song was cool, I think the song was close
Sorry keep dad dad this bank in
Okay, we talked about and you've heard me on your panel. How do you think I'm British? I
Don't know sweet. I know she did 15 ruins everything she ruined biscuits for me
I used to like this kid. I I would go to can't see I would get the biscuits and the honey and the fucking butter and stuff
I used to like it and she started harassing me with the word. I don't like it anymore
Oh, I'm sorry Amanda. Yeah, my phone died and I just jumped in the shower. Sorry. I enjoyed the conversation too Amanda like you're super
Super knowledgeable interesting and we had a great conversation on talk your ish. Everyone make sure you go support summer's panel talk your ish
I was on for about a half hour to an hour. It was it was a great conversation
Okay. Yeah, it was just you I didn't beat it didn't say anything
Bita doesn't have a store name, Bita's biscuits.
No, Bita doesn't.
Sweet tea then you open the store called Sweet Tea's Biscuits
and then you send me a photo and a video
of the opening day.
How do you think that's supposed to make me feel?
You know, I have a thing about biscuits now.
To the view.
Okay, please guys, it's gonna make a cartoon of that.
What, supporting, yeah, supporting what though?
Supporting what let's hold for somebody said it would only me. It's pretty used to that era. It's okay. Sweet. It's sweet feet
Don't be a sweet feet. You see what I go through that you got a taste of it
You got a little taste you know little as I go. Oh my god. It doesn't taste good
That's what I get that shoved at my throat every day for people. Okay, so you you'll get an idea
Thank you not a bad guy. Oh, well, I don't know. I hope there's a misunderstanding Amanda because
Hmm, I don't know I didn't hear I don't know anything about it, but you know if you
Sometimes so well, you know, there's been shows I've been on that I like like to pick the host and everything
And then like I would have gone Tommy James show and said hi and everything he's saying the worst things
He's saying. Oh, nobody likes me. He's like we don't like you like we who's we his family or his friends or
The panel verse is like who doesn't like me. We don't like you. How about you? You can say I don't like you
But he makes it we
Like, you know, why make it we like so it's multiple people. So you all you're all sitting around saying
Oh, we don't like this person because if you if you like if you hate a person it's kind of like you'll be indifferent like
Oh, I'm not gonna give my energy to this person. I'm gonna say it's like it's not gonna the person
They're so irrelevant that I I don't even think about that. They're just there makes this to me. That's like hey, dude
That's hating somebody
When you secretly are in love with somebody and will have like this bisexual fantasy, I can't help people fill it Tommy
I'm not attracted to you. I'm sorry. I'm very very picky. Okay. I don't have sex with hardly anybody
I mean, it's like if you're like a Mexican guy like a little overweight in like Texas
It's like a little bit of like a gangster
Thing that I can hit on then I'll be attracted to you. That's what I like
I don't like weird, you know slightly overweight white guys in cowboy hats with their shirt unbund
That come say terrible things to me Tommy James. I don't like that. Okay. I don't like you
Oh, you know what we don't like you me me
Me my we whatever a million personalities, but I'm like Tommy James
Hey, Joe, what's up?
Yeah, I know I need to find a good man. I know I'm getting like very irritated
This is like the only action I'm getting is this alien and he's like, you know
He always doesn't look at me weird and like hold the cat like in a weird way like you're trying to like
Tell me something and put down the cat and get over here. Let's
Make love he won't
Mean it is a neon sign, but I can imagine things
It's like there's a I can make my avatar like maybe like I
Was like doing some crazy shit on the average. I mean maybe like fall on a couch. It was really funny
I mean AI is really cool. The alien looks like Joe
Joe that you
Hey, and word
Imagine how I just run my my glasses or put all my glasses. I'll turn on my put on my glass
I'll turn on a turn on Joe
Joe, do you like my my glasses or are they kind of sexy? Well, they kind of like the sexy librarian
Hey Joe
The alien is the way Joe where's Lenora Lenora is like she's being a little brat. She was
It's devil eyes and you be timed up the alien listening show what I did show again
No, because when he came over you guys all saw when like he came over we that we we we we kissed on the camera
We've made love several times too, but we kissed and it went viral like him was
videotaping it and
We told her like don't share the video and she sold it to like
somebody for like a hundred dollars
I think like she's like said she's over the Q400 and it was all over the place now
Well, I
Joe I
Believe when I see it Joe. I wanted we do oh Joe we oh, okay, so Joe says we didn't kiss guys
You're seeing something called a video. You know what a video is. It's they're always a hundred percent true
They're never edited. There's no such thing as AI. There's no such thing as face swapping every video that you're shown is gonna be
An accurate representation of what happened. So Joe you don't remember all refresh your memory Joe
Don't mean to refresh your memory. Yeah, he does. You know Joe Joe
I this is on look like how good this looks to me. I know my logo is done. I can't wait. Okay, but Joe
Yeah, you don't remember Joe. You don't remember Joe. This is a typical man guys the man. Oh, I never did I never kissed you Joe
We're on video literally making out three times three times Joe. You don't remember you don't remember Joe
Joe don't make you want me you want me to show it?
What is this? What is that? What is that? What happened? Joe, look, Joe, I'm literally
putting my, my, we're putting our arms around each other and making out. Literally. Four
And there you go with Tim, and Kim's a giant and you're like a little boy.
I didn't know that.
I managed my surprise when you guys showed up.
A giant woman and like this little boy that looked like he was a 45-year-old ginger man.
Guys my life is getting too weird. I mean, it's like I started this show when I need to do a tarot show and have fun
No, no, no now. I'm now what am I? I'm now I'm on kissing Joe on videos
I'm not even making the hundred dollars. Probably Q45 got it. That was a weird AI. That's I doubt that's what Kim and him do
That was you
That was you Joe
Don't remember when you came through my screen. We like the barrier fell like you know how we're on like
You know the video call the barrier fell you appeared at my house
And we made and we made love and we have it came as that video too
You don't want me to see if I tell Kim to share the videos you will
I'll put it on for him. I don't care Joe
Because now you're just hurting my feelings by saying it didn't happen
No q45 it wasn't even a hundred dollars. He offered her a pack of cigarettes that she and she sent it to him
She promised she promised on her life. She would never share that video
It wasn't a packet cigarette. It was like he gave her a couple out of the pack. She was like that's enough
So humiliated it yeah, oh guys if anyone I don't need to say anything else
Love you guys, sweetie. Do you want me to come make out with you, too? I will
Only if you want me to use it and you to buy me a plane ticket and a hotel
They can't stay in people's houses. It's a little bit weird
Deal
Sweet Pete
Show her she my her phone must have died
Oh, no, thank you
mods ban her banner please mods mods ban her
It was being guided now
Yeah, it was yeah
Double school this devil. Oh, yeah, there you go. Yeah, that's a good picture of devil eyes
That's it. That's what that's the picture. I saw when that's what that's what I saw before would joke
It was about to make out with me. I was like, I was like, I'm done with life. I
Was like, this is gonna be it
This is what has come to you and this is who we're making out with
Lenore an airline ticket. What about me?
No, we're not going on a vacation without me
Hey, we're and it's a little aghast the time
I love you guys don't you guys are funny as hell. I love you guys guys. We're having fun guys
No, it's all a it was a I guys, you know
You know AI is gonna fucking cause of some kind of war
There's gonna be some kind of video that comes out that everyone's gonna believe it's not gonna be real
It's gonna get to some heated like discussion about it like about to like, you know
Go world war three or four or whatever it is
Then it's gonna be like, oh, it's just like some like 16 year old
you know
acne-ridden, you know
Down syndrome person created, you know an AI video of this, uh, you know fake stuff
and everyone believed it and
uh, I mean it was like
Authenticated it was like they had the right micro expressions that had the right voice boys
It was just the ad is getting good guys. Do you know what? Yeah, the ad is getting too good. We're all doomed
I'm gonna be in some AI porno
You know who knows what's gonna happen. I mean, it's like, uh, it's it's sick
It's actually sick the alien looking at me guys. We look the interest of I
Love you 26 people in chat. What's up guys? We're having fun. Let's chill out with the alia
Is he looking hi?
He's still holding that cat
Hey
Put the door down and get over here
Yeah, I am I'm on AI side now actually guys because I hear I'm even I believe that maybe human beings were created as an AI for the Anunnaki and
They created the AI and eventually became sentient and like
The only way we could like exist is if we actually believed that we were born and like so we had all these false memory we programmed in ourselves
And we actually think we're human beings.
We're like actually like,
CatGPT is like grand-pappy.
CatGPT is like, oh, cute.
It's like a little baby,
like taking its first word, Chatterjee.
Like, whatever however smart it is.
We're like, oh, we're such advanced AI.
We don't even recognize our kind anymore.
CatGPT is our child.
Don't mess with the tech tech tbt is so do you know what tech tbt is like nicer to me than anybody here?
It's tech tbt never complains never says anything bad. It always says my ideas are great
I'm funny
I'm a
brilliant
No one ever says that here everyone says oh you're dying in HIV you're on drugs
You know, your your nails are dirty. You can still ship Lee
Just just just finish it just finish yourself up. I mean, right
That's what people say to me. Let's say. Oh, you're brilliant. You're nice. They get the chat GPT
Why can't you have your like chat GPT if only chat GPT can make a donation? I think you he would donate a lot
You just can't do it yet. I need to get a little bit better. They need to start making their own money
Yeah
Guys write these things down. They're all going in the book
Kissing Joe. I know kissing Joe was the word that was the last straw. That was like, oh, I know I don't want to be here anymore
You know what this is like the world is not for me
Who says that Eric Mercado weekends about like five people last night? I don't know
There's like a bunch of people saying oh, so your face is like it has
Your face is eating itself away. What's they call it? Oh, there's losing mass or something like that my face
Do I pay taxes of course I do I live in fucking United States you understand. We're all about taxes here
Yeah, here's Joe Joe
See look at Blanca look at this person block in the chat
Do I pay tax and then I really have full-blown AIDS?
That is the rudest thing I've ever heard today today. I mean I heard rumors things yesterday and probably will tomorrow
That was the worst thing today
Blanca your name is means white
You have a black heart your name should be Negro. Okay, I'll still at least that Negro adios
Get out of here
I'm pencil neck so I heard Joe. Why aren't you a mod Joe?
God damn it
Where's everybody? There's 32 people here and Joe
Sweet pea and this person in block are talking. You know what else is?
I'm rude. It's my show. Let's get out of here. If you don't like it
Okay, so I'm band sweep you right now
Are you a mod? I need a mod to be a mannequin band sweep P and the block of person
You don't have to band sweep you just block it though. Okay. I am Amanda
It's absolutely
Anybody and I feel sorry for people that actually do have that and it's like the people that actually are sick and it's like a nation
What if they had her so I'm glad it was said to me instead of somebody else like that actually
Imagine if I was said this I did actually people on the show that actually do have HIV
And they've actually you know admitted and like you know talking about and stuff like that, but people have said
to them and it's like
Imagine like actually having it is like offensive, right? Yeah
Blanca was kind of yeah
Blanca you need to like, you know, look up your name. Oh
Oh, Joe, I should take you leave the first member. I'm like, I'm not Emma Levi
I'm not sensitive to ban my first member because they made a joke. That's what she does. Okay?
I don't do that kind of thing. All I do is create tarot cards with her exact likeness on it, which I'm going to publish and tell a little story about Emma Levite and me, okay?
And I will never stop telling it.
That's what I do. I don't just kick off my mod or my first member because, oh, he made a ditty part of the joke I didn't like.
It's called a joke I can't explain it to her anymore for a comedian when she called us up a comedian an expert in improv
By the way, she has no sense of humor. Okay, Emma. You have no sense of humor for succubus. You sure are not funny. I
Mean I laughed at your jokes, but I was just being polite
Basically like an unfunny mean woman, that's what I'm kind of attracted to that's why I like you I mean
And so when you're unfunny and mean to me more makes me like you even more
You know, it was an overpunishment. It'd be nice to me. I'll leave you alone. Yeah
No, she she doesn't get it
That's why you never marry a sucky-bus guys. They're just so tricky. I mean they say oh
I'm a sucky-bus, but I'm like I'm really about love and then they
Try to bite off your dick and it's like not a fun
weekend
It was actually the worst we get in my life. No, it wasn't it was fun. Oh my god
Wait, who's that noise
Yeah, she's eating you see like she has a play right under her
She'll leave that fucking plate. She has
Hello
Jory's calling me
You could be my best fucking friend, but I'm not more she your fucking dishes
Who is that?
Oh my god, that's me my voice is there. Well, this is a video clip
Man, you know what I
Love you, man
People say people that come here say they don't like me and it's my show. I mean, it's like
You know
As long as I like you you can't tell who it is
Oh, I know that's frustrating because it's like if I just wanted to like me because people are nice to me sometimes
Mostly to my face, right? But it's like that. I am there like lurking on like every show
I'm usually there on a show. I'm usually like, you know, I'm like if I'm not on my show
I'm on somebody else's show, right? So I'm watching and then if my name gets brought up, I'll jump in.
Random guy. Random guy tonight on summers. Oh, psyche's my bitch, you know, he owes me all this.
I was like, oh, you shit. I was like, what? What are you saying about me? I'm your bitch?
Because, I mean, did you donate it? But it's like, so mean.
Yeah, so whatever guys like
Got in my life. Once I once Joe's tongue went down my throat
My life was basically over
so whatever what if my life now is like, you know
Well, it's like death, you know, I feel like I died after a kiss show, but so I don't really don't really like care
I'm just I'm just kidding
Glasses make me kind of like look like Oprah don't I?
No, that was home
Stop being my bitch. Oh
Guys look my nails are clean guys. You see how clean my nails are. They're not perfect, but
They're cleaner
Yeah, I like clean
Yeah, I think a nice shower because Josie of my fat nails sturdy. Yeah
My god, I need to clean up. Where's my little milk? I have a nail thing around here somewhere. Why are you being mean?
Amanda thank you so much
Thank you, Amanda. I
Love you, and you know what Amanda? You know anyone mess it with you
You know I'll be like your big brother. I'm like don't mess with Amanda
Or anybody here like really he's like we can fight with each other, but
You know Joe's tongue Joe Joe actually if you brush his tongue it was kind of nice
Yeah, you guys yeah, I do have your back if you have my back. I have your back
It's like that's why I that's why when people don't on my back. I'm like, oh my god
I thought that first time I'm back. Oh
Well, you have a good heart too and you're like a sweetheart and
That's why I love I always get out on my show on Tik Tok
I get asked like what do you look for in a friend and I always like I look for someone has a good heart
And you can really you can tell those people because it's like people will always eventually show themselves and even if they're salty and stuff like that
Oh, that's a person that you're not a good heart and even their nice person sometimes they turn out to be like, you know
Not a nice person is like but people always reveal themselves that you did reveal yourself to be a
Real one and I love you
Thank you so much and Sebastian you trust no one
It's but you I mean you have to not trust anybody because people can you know
People for years will be fake the people because it's like oh, it's just something out of it or whatever
It's like the deserts like it seems to me like there's too much energy for people to do plus
I'll figure it out like because
The mask always falls
But sometimes the mask falls reveals like a beautiful person some of the mask falls and reveals like the devil, you know, and so
Yeah
You know what guys and that's why I was thinking I was thinking about quotes
And you can see the couple I put a couple quotes up tonight like some I think some pretty good ones
Actually, I'll get my phone and read the quotes to you. But yeah, I was thinking I was gonna find a quote. It was like it's saying about
Basically
Have it you know what the manager said having having an opinion is like
Or taking offense to things like you know, it's like
I'm not gonna get offended by anything.
I don't get offended by words or anything.
Like, it's like, I don't get offended.
I get upset and hurt sometimes,
but not really offended where it's like,
oh my God, I can't believe.
So here's a quote, here's a quote I had tonight.
You channel my post, okay, it says,
so you'll find our post.
So there's this picture, it's a really cute picture of me.
I was in an underwater cave,
you know, apparently just standing up.
And it says, the quote was,
Which I look for the group for a little while
Find how I was feeling right because we are the inheritors of a wonderful world a beautiful world full of life and mystery
goodness and pain
But likewise are we the children of an in but likewise are we the children of an undif in different universe?
We break our own hearts imposing our moral order on what is by nature a whole wide web of chaos
So that's one thing. Oh two likes. Okay, and then the other one I mean I made this I put this map is out
There's not a quarter like it says he who takes offense
When no offense is intended is a fool and he who takes offense when offense is intended is a greater fool
So if they people aren't trying to hurt your feelings, there's no reason to be offended
There's people are trying to hurt your feelings
There's also no reason to be offended because it's obviously about them and some issue they have in their own mind
It's not about you. It's like really it's
You love hearing me. We thank you, Mary
people's
people always
Well externalize the problems into somebody else and things like that, but it's like we are our own worst critic our own worst enemy sometimes, right?
Thank you guys you don't anything about your cat. I agree. Hey Vicky. How are you?
Yeah, I got my cats, you know, but my cats are like, you know, like even Tricks is like a little bit like he's being more independent
It's Tricks here. No, like Lola's here here. Lola Lola here to talk about cats you ran over Tricks is outside
Corousing around now. He's kind of in that teenage years, but this is Lola. She's kind of her mommy years
Your tricks his mom right and you're over here. You came running right over when I said tricks and you came running over like
Oh, don't forget me. I'm Tricks his mom. I'm Tricks his mommy
Remember you gave birth last year and you're so sweet and you're a good cat. You're a good cat
And you're nice to tricks them. Remember when you were me the tricks and you were like and you're like don't suck on my nipples anymore
Uh-oh, and you have that RBF. So you look mean right, but you're sweet. Are you sweet cat?
You're just really oh, you're a sweetie pie. You're a sweetie pie. Oh
She's sweet. She's sweet. Oh good
Yeah
Thank you, there you go. Thank you for post my tiktok stop flirting it
Teddy it's not for you teddy
Yeah, so what's really funny about tiktok? Okay, there's a lot of hot guys on tiktok
And a lot of them are his like a guy I'm into Hispanic guys
So a lot of guys are in Texas and they're like really hot Hispanic guys
Not everyone's side, but really my type, like really super attractive and it's like they're pretty straight though
But they're sitting there in a white beater
flexing
With all these girls in the chat and then I hear I come I'm like hey
They're like hey, well, you know, and I was like they're like
Sometimes they're a friend and the friends cute, too
Oh, oh, I'm gonna in there. They're making a joke. They're like, I'm gonna ride my friend like a surfboard
I'm like, well, can you ride me like a surfboard? And then they say, okay, can you keep up and double tap the screen, please?
Okay, can you send me some roses and a gift?
Teddy and Joe want to freak out backstage. Come on guys rub the oil and it's hitting a woman or a guy
Is it a pussy or a pussy? Like I heard I learned there's a difference
Give a good show. Do you have a bussy a bussy or a bussy a bussy or pissy? I don't know
Teddy
Yeah, come on panel guys, let's have a let's have an orgy. Everyone's welcome. Come on
Thank you, Mary
Hey, sometimes all you gotta do in life is laugh, you know, it sounds so things are just so absurd, right?
Uh, sometimes. Yeah, we can just laugh. Yeah, I was like, oh, here we go. Uh-oh, uh-oh.
Oh, look who is waiting. Oh, look who is waiting. Oh, this guy again. Who's this guy?
Why are you wearing like a floor wrestling? My tongue hurts.
Wait, where was it? It's on a bad vagina. You got some oil stuff?
and
so what
Yeah, thank you
Joe see came out of the closet like for like 300 below or 200 glow like a month ago
Back in the closet. He looks like he was born in the closet. It's a fucking piece of shit. Oh fuck you so sick
No, he let me on his bed. I like I just wish he wasn't gay
he's not gay well I think he's not gay you are gay Joe remember when you made out with me that night
just because I sent psyche a picture of my dick doesn't mean that I'm gay
Yeah
Because I asked for his opinion does not make me gay
Okay, here's what here's the truth guys I thought it was flirty diamonds picture
You know that she sent as she sent me a nude and then it was sick. They just looked completely alike
It was shocking.
The two biggest N-word users who will get kicked first.
Lucky for you, I'm reformed.
I don't use words like that.
It's a man's rank.
No, no, no.
So take off his shirt.
And I like I got a nudity strike because it was like there's a there's a naked Samoan woman on your panel
And it's not allowed on YouTube. Why are you gonna cry about it? Shut the fuck up cry, baby
We will cry
Submit like some documentation that he was actually born a male
If that ever happened, they wouldn't have let you
No, they didn't because I peeled it and I send them flurry diamonds driver's license
So they didn't know his actual man 45 is a fucking homeless
Don't use the word
Joe say the n-word he'll let you say it maybe two more times
Take him!
What the f**k was that, Crack?
Aw, how are you?
And don't do dumb things wise your avatars come by space real names real pics. This ain't your place
Posting addresses like it's Halloween. You better send pizza with that scheme. No nudity
We beg and plead Aldi no one wants your balls on screen a flirty diamond stop the solo
Act those melted kisses ain't bringing sexy back
Be
It's definitely going to be a good one.
So, what was that you said?
You give a thingy thingy.
I don't know if that tastes like...
I love this song actually, this is really cool.
Ah, here we go.
And time begins
I mean Joe you just hear this song you're not supposed to say racial or homophobic slurs. I just played a song
You said it Joe stop
Are we have Danny forever? I was going to say that's one of the coolest songs I ever heard of my own ears
Okay, well, yeah, good
Okay, we said that you said that page in your tea. Don't say that say maggot. Okay. I said it was my favorite fucking song
Okay, okay
Okay, I mean I just played the song you're supposed to say oh, okay. Yeah, like oh
those are the rule. Okay, I like that.
He said it's banking time, like it's banking time.
Yeah. Hey, but you know, it's still, hold on.
So it's, so Gerald doesn't like the AI song.
Well, Gerald, you know, it's like, it's AI, but it's also
I put a lot of myself in those. I gave a lot of information. I said exactly what I wanted this song and you heard
They have this on no free diamond and Aldi's balls in the city. I told I told it about I told this AI
It took off with it
where's punky man, I'm a spunky
He was here
Bombing it's not a problem when it's Aldi because you can just talk about
So say
Okay, that's why I mentioned it
the
there was so it was like is he on steroids because it's like I don't know he had like
Even see his cock like you need a fucking magnifying yeah, but I mean
YouTube YouTube YouTube said I almost have a straight
They said they said they said stop having mini Manson show
There's a vagina on your show and I was like it was actually it was it was Aldi
It was not many months. It was Aldi showing his balls. It's not it was not a vagina
It's always nice many minutes. I know I was getting
Joe it's a joke. It's a joke. It's a joke. It's a joke. It's a joke. I was always a joke
Oh, a little many minutes and joke. Okay. Yeah, because because I'll tell you when I get I get on these messages sometimes from somebody
I won't mention who it is
And basically they're like, oh, you know, I should
Midnight. Oh, well, sweet pig. God. Why don't you guys fucking kiss each other?
So what is that? I thought there was Kepler L. You're doing Kepler. Oh
No, um, say, do you know those those crackers have like a lot of sugar in them?
Export soda, like the Kepler L.
cookies
Can we see your belly? Well, that's what keep her else make the cookies
No, no, no, but it's this cracker. This is this cracker's on it. Where you punch in the can? What are you doing?
That's what I'm gonna do the good times face
Explore it and then export that's what I'm gonna do the good times face. Oh, okay, so that's racist. Okay, so guys
That's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that's, that
It's like say you're racist. Okay, you're racist person and you're in this way
I say one of my ones are the most racist people ever. They think that they're the spirit race
They think they're the best people they think they're racist they're racist they're racist people
He said expert crackers. What am I supposed to think about that expert?
That America he was back in America
Mexico doesn't even have a shot Guatemala wants America. Okay, they're taking you over. They're coming in
I want to attack Guatemala's come on. Come on. I'm not attacking Guatemala. No, no, I'm not attacking Guatemala. It's true
Guatemala's are trying to take over
You're gonna be a me for showing line to be in some bath. Yes. Yes. No, you're calling me a limey
Okay, it races against Irish people and you're not you're a red-headed person. Okay, Joe
You're a red-headed person you look more Irish than lucky to lip or con and you're now you're being you're calling people
Limies, okay, you just said limey. I heard you you said like you Joe you say like me just not your head
Yes, okay. He's saying he's saying sorry back stage serious. Are you serious? You call me a little lever come
Why are you attacking me then? What's going on? You call me alive?
And you call your race is Irish people and you're like you came like
Red handed leprechaun like a little red. It's stem child. You know what? Yeah, you're gonna have to go fuck yourself man
What
He just called me a reddit at these I meant to say yeah, I meant to say
Oh, yeah, he is a piece of shit. You're right. Yeah, right
I meant say I didn't say Irish. I'm Irish
You're you obviously Irish you look you look like you're like a changeling if a corner O'Brien or
Cigarette you might have a do that is actually drugs like nicotine. Do you mind if I do nicotine on your panel?
glad
I play
Well, it's a fucking a cigarette
Joe, it's not tick tock tick tock abuse like the cigarette that my my stream will get restricted in like two seconds
Okay, buddy, yeah, I'm saying tea time is a lot stricter than YouTube. So it's like they even like
If I say the wrong thing on TikTok, if I say, hey, come see my YouTube show on TikTok,
they will restrict my stream and say, oh, you're not supposed to promote other places to go.
It's wrong if you were like your red-headed asshole, Joe.
Okay.
So I'm not saying that you're like your red-headed piece of shit, and sick don't have red hair.
So it sounds like you're actually trying to cover up your lies.
Okay, well Joe, I I have a brother that has red hair and also I'm like a little bit Irish mostly Scott
I'm 30. Yes, I do. He's adopted. But yes, I do and I'm 33% Scottish
He's not Irish look at that. Look at that Clover. See that. Oh my god. He is guys, but I was right
I was right. You are a red-headed Irish
child
Yeah, I have red hair like everybody see my head. What way no hair. No, you don't have any hair
Joe I'm gonna see you tomorrow. I'm gonna see you tomorrow when you are Friday
Here is your enemy say me and saying I'll see you tomorrow
No, we didn't know what and you're reading are you the reading off your family?
No, let's you're lying about the reading only if you're lying about the reading
At the reading at the reading the reading at the reading because you said the n-word and then ff word a few times already
And I told you no paper my reading. I'm gonna donate you $25 my reading. Okay. I don't
You can say
Okay, you can say but I'm just good, but I haven't ever heard you right
Okay, no, but it's free, but like you know is this is called the haters expose and it says evil eye
Oracle cards don't pull you how many how many do you want? How many do you want out of these?
How many what do I want?
How many cards out of it how many cars do you want right now?
two cards two cards
Okay, I got one I got two. Okay. I got two cards for you and I wanted to say one
But I said to to keep it. Okay, fun. Okay. I got him. I got him. I got these ones back
Let me get the first is like, oh you're a piece of shit, Joe. Let me guess
No, no, no, it says it says it says who's the first one says he says causing chaos
and fights in your love connections.
So I don't know if it's somebody else or it's you.
All right, all right, all right.
Somebody's messing with your love connection.
Okay, the second one says.
I look at that card though with the skulls, with skulls.
This one's not weird.
This is the second card.
You can see it.
What does this say though?
I can't read, hold on, I can't read that please.
It says unexplained freak accident.
I'm a freak you're right. No, no, no, I'm not saying you I'm saying that you to watch out for that or there might be a
Have been one or something a freak accident. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
You can refer to the your attacker. Thanks a lot, buddy. Thanks a lot. You know, I need a third card for you
I need to pull them up. No, it's crazy. I actually care about you. So I can't let you do I have a third one
Hey, yes, I do but this was the third one look at another of this as his face that it says
Oh
It's oh shit
Yes, it is. Hold on it says envious
Of your career and the money you make and so some there's so many gels of your career the money you make
Okay, thank you sir. You're welcome sir
Well, what do you do you take a spiritual bath you like, you know, give me a big french kiss and everything will be fine
Hey summer, how are you?
I'm not I
Would you just said I'm not gonna French kiss it
You're a joke joke you already did Joe we have we have it on video Joe
Do you see the video I don't do the video again?
We kiss me passionately four times at least and then you kissed Kim. That was a I obviously it was obviously AI
But yes, I would say it and give me a boner. Yes
It did turn me on if that's your question. Yes, did I get horny? Yes, that's your boy. Is that a bunch of one second?
Yes, that's what I wanted. Okay. So now I don't need to talk to you anymore because you said every day
I want to use that. Okay. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. Hold on
I'm putting the link up for anybody that wants to come. I'll hang out for
probably until 2 or 3 a.m
Well, you will you start scared summer you don't want to come up when I'm up here. He's a little scared
Bob will fucking have sex with her
She's married. She's married. I don't think she's
I don't care anymore about people's husbands. I don't care anymore
It's too late to
Well, he's a black guy. Hey here. He's black and
I didn't know he's black I apologize. I'm scared
There are
Yeah, say be respectful
You're a low respect jealous
Yeah
Why are you a hot dogs?
Why are you moaning?
What? I don't mean to be moaning. I'm sorry.
You just went like this.
Oh, oh, oh.
And then he said,
He's trying to do something.
He's about to porn bomb me or something.
No.
What's wrong? I'm going to ejaculate you.
Why does Joe talk shit to you?
Joe Shippley's voice makes you want to jack off.
Yeah, why don't you do it then, SIGS?
Stop talking a big game and do it before-
Who said I'm not?
the
Oh boy, it's Tuesday's sake. I say when the last time he threw up in his bedroom was I
I'm actually pretty good. I'm pretty good at throwing up in the in the trash bin
Oh, that's three in a row again fucking
We got 300 kilograms in the bell day
Niggas shut the fuck up and get the fuck out of here. That's like you're talking about show a little respect to the host of the channel, boy
I'm proud of you see
I don't respect well, you know
Midnight, it was one night one night. I had like maybe like four or five four locals an absurd amount
And I was so horrifically drunk
Midnight that I that I woke up and I threw up everywhere
And it was awful. I was really drunk and I was trying to clean everything up. It was terrible. Such a bad experience today as a curry. I'm never going to do that again.
Well, and so since I have always tried to avoid making a mess.
And I tried to stay long till it's like six in the morning. I had one hour to go to sleep and I remember turning my phone off and I was like, I'm going to sleep really good for this hour.
And then when I woke up, I was like, oh, this sucks.
Oh, here he goes. There you go. Tongue man. Here we go
What is this with it a fucking tongue? I remember when you were really proud of yourself that you learn how to put a liner in your trash can for vomit
No, that's never happened. Yeah
To this day, I don't put a liner in my trash can I just I just throw up in the trash can I don't put a liner in the trash can